quiz_data_2 = [
    {
        "question": "What is the primary management of Burns?",
        "choices": ["Hold Under Cool Running Water", "Apply Blister Lotion", "Hold Under Cold Compress", " DRSABCD"],
        "answer": "Hold Under Cool Running Water"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is not part of the asthma treatment?",
        "choices": ["Provide Water", "Assist With Medication", "Encourage Light Movements", "Breathing Exericises"],
        "answer": "Encourage Light Movements"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hypoglycaemia is characterised by:",
        "choices": ["High Blood Sugar", "Low Blood Sugar", "High Insulin Levels", "Low Insulin Levels"],
        "answer": "Low Blood Sugar"
    },
    {
        "question": "What medical condition includes an epipen in its treatment?",
        "choices": ["Diabetes", "Poisoning", "Epileptic Seizures", "Anaphylaxis"],
        "answer": "Anaphylaxis"
    },
    {
        "question": "How would an area be adjusted for a patient in an epileptic seizure?",
        "choices": ["Increase Room Temperature", "Lower Room Temperature", "Clear The Area Around the Patient", " Turn Off All Lights"],
        "answer": "Clear The Area Around the Patient"
    },
    {
        "question": "If swallowed poision, in what scenario should you induce vomiting?",
        "choices": ["When Substance is Medicinal", "When Substance is Corrosive", "When Substance is Unkown", "When Substance is Hot in Temperature"],
        "answer": "When Substance is Medicinal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these are not part of hypothermia treatment?",
        "choices": ["Drinking Warm Fluids", "Remove Any Wet Clothing", "Utilise Artificial Heating", "DRSABCD"],
        "answer": "Utilise Artificial Heating"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of bandage should be used for a snakebite?",
        "choices": ["Collar and Cuff", "Pressure Immobilisation", "Reptillian Power Wrap", "Elastic Bandaging"],
        "answer": "Pressure Immobilisation"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is RICER (rest, ice, compress, elevate, referral) used for?",
        "choices": ["Concussions and Head Injuries", "Eye Injuries", "Fractures and Dislocations", "Chemical Burns"],
        "answer": "Fractures and Dislocations"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does RICER stand for",
        "choices": ["Rest, Ice, Compress, Elevate, Referral", " Rest, Ice, Cover, Elevate, Re-Ice", "Rest, Ice, Compress, Extend, Referral", "Relieve, Ice, Comfort, Elevate, Referral"],
        "answer": "Rest, Ice, Compress, Elevate, Referral"
    }
    # Add more questions here
]